<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>pwnbuffer</title>
    <link>https://pwnbuffer.org/en/</link>
    <description>Recent content on pwnbuffer</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 08 May 2025 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="https://pwnbuffer.org/en/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Malware analysis - Kimsuky (NORTH KOREAN APT)</title>
      <link>https://pwnbuffer.org/en/posts/c/exploring-kimsuky-malware/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 08 May 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://pwnbuffer.org/en/posts/c/exploring-kimsuky-malware/</guid>
      <description>SUMMARY: Link to heading Introduction Technical Analysis 2.1. C# Injection with Add-Type 2.2. Process Hiding via ShowWindow 2.3. Base64 Obfuscation and Dynamic Execution 2.4. Distraction PDF and Social Engineering 2.5. External Tools and Payload Extraction 2.6. Multi-stage Payload Execution 2.7. Final Stage Script Execution MITRE ATT&amp;amp;CK Mapping Final Thoughts 1. INTRODUCTION Link to heading APT refers to Advanced Persistent Threat groups known for highly advanced and stealthy malware. The sample analyzed here is tagged as APT, Kimsuky, and written in PowerShell (.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>x86 Part. 2 — Number System</title>
      <link>https://pwnbuffer.org/en/posts/neurosys/x86-2/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 04 May 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://pwnbuffer.org/en/posts/neurosys/x86-2/</guid>
      <description>Welcome to the second part of our series of articles on Basic Reverse Engineering! Link to heading ██ ██ █████ ██████ ██ ██ ██ ██ ██ ███ █████ ███████ ██ ██ ██ ██ ██ ██ ██ ██ █████ ██████ Now that we&amp;rsquo;ve explored the fundamental concepts of CPU in the first article, it&amp;rsquo;s time to understand how data is represented and manipulated internally by computers. Let&amp;rsquo;s talk about numbering systems, with a focus on hexadecimal, which is crucial for those working with low-level reverse engineering.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Review of assembly</title>
      <link>https://pwnbuffer.org/en/posts/slayer/assembly-review/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 30 Apr 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://pwnbuffer.org/en/posts/slayer/assembly-review/</guid>
      <description>What is assembly? Link to heading Assembly is a low-level programming language, it is written to communicate directly with the processor hardware. Unlike high-level languages, such as the famous Python, assembly operates close to machine code, the famous binary! Each assembly instruction generally represents a single CPU operation, such as moving data between registers, performing arithmetic operations or controlling the flow of execution.&#xA;Assembly is not universal!! It depends directly on the processor architecture.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bypassing Linux Kernel Defenses</title>
      <link>https://pwnbuffer.org/en/posts/black0ut/kernel_linux_bypass/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 Apr 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://pwnbuffer.org/en/posts/black0ut/kernel_linux_bypass/</guid>
      <description>lights off &amp;amp; black0ut on&#xA;1- Introduction Link to heading Hello, Welcome!!!&#xA;In this article, I will discuss how modern protections in the Linux Kernel hinder and mitigate rootkit functionalities, and of course, how to bypass them.&#xA;2- Kernel Address Space Layout Randomization (KASLR) Link to heading As one of the primary defense mechanisms of the Kernel and other systems, it randomizes the kernel&amp;rsquo;s memory addresses on each boot, making exploitation more difficult for attackers.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>x86 Part. 1 — CPU</title>
      <link>https://pwnbuffer.org/en/posts/neurosys/x86/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 30 Mar 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://pwnbuffer.org/en/posts/neurosys/x86/</guid>
      <description>This series of articles covers basic low-level concepts in computers, with a specific focus on exploring binaries and reverse engineering. Some points may seem confusing at first, but remember: everything follows a definition. Don’t get stuck in an endless loop of &amp;ldquo;why!?!&amp;rdquo; — just understand each concept and its purpose. You will use these concepts in reverse engineering, binary exploitation, and even malware development in the future.&#xA;What is a CPU?</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Privilege Escalation in Linux</title>
      <link>https://pwnbuffer.org/en/posts/slayer/privesc-linux/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 22 Mar 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://pwnbuffer.org/en/posts/slayer/privesc-linux/</guid>
      <description>Hi, I&amp;rsquo;m Slayer. In this paper, I will talk about privilege escalation in Linux. I recommend that, while reading this paper, also go testing the techniques in practice, as this will help to better understand the concepts and apply the knowledge acquired more effectively.&#xA;Introduction Link to heading Privilege escalation is the process of gaining higher levels of access or control on a system than originally allowed. On Linux systems, this often involves elevating a common user to root privileges or exploiting poorly configured permissions to access restricted resources.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Writeup THM - Dragon Byte</title>
      <link>https://pwnbuffer.org/en/posts/slayer/writeup-dragonbyte/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 09 Mar 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://pwnbuffer.org/en/posts/slayer/writeup-dragonbyte/</guid>
      <description>https://tryhackme.com/room/dragonbyte&#xA;In this paper, I&amp;rsquo;m going to take you step by step through the Dragon Byte room, made by brother NullByte! From recon to root!&#xA;Reconnaissance Link to heading After starting the machine and obtaining the IP, the first thing we have to do is port scanning. In this CTF I used the RustScan tool to do the port scanning:&#xA;This scan revealed that we have 3 open ports, namely:</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rootkits in Firmware</title>
      <link>https://pwnbuffer.org/en/posts/slayer/rootkits-firmware/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 05 Mar 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://pwnbuffer.org/en/posts/slayer/rootkits-firmware/</guid>
      <description>What is a Rootkit? Link to heading A rootkit is a type of malware designed to gain and maintain privileged access to a system while hiding its presence. The term comes from the combination of &amp;ldquo;root&amp;rdquo;, which refers to the user with maximum privileges on Linux systems, and &amp;ldquo;kit&amp;rdquo; which represents a set of tools used to control the compromised system&#xA;The main purpose of a rootkit is to ensure persistence, allowing an attacker to continue accessing the system even after reboots or removal attempts.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Windows Architecture</title>
      <link>https://pwnbuffer.org/en/posts/tteuw/windows_architecture/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 08 Feb 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://pwnbuffer.org/en/posts/tteuw/windows_architecture/</guid>
      <description>Prerequisites: Requirements for the users that are planning to learn Malware Development are first of all basics of programming, since mostly deals with the C programming lanaguage, it is a requirement that you are familiar with fundamentals of C.&#xA;So what is actually Windows Architecture? It is what happens under the hood of Windows processes and applications, the internal structure of the Windows operating system, envolves layers like hardware, kernel, executive services, and subsystem DLLs.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>buffer overflow in practice</title>
      <link>https://pwnbuffer.org/en/posts/slayer/bof/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 07 Feb 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://pwnbuffer.org/en/posts/slayer/bof/</guid>
      <description>What is buffer overflow? Link to heading Buffer overflow (BOF) is one of the most wellknown and historically significant vulnerabilities in the world of cybersecurity. It occurs when a program writes more data to a buffer than it can hold, causing memory corruption. This flaw can be exploited by pentesters to execute arbitrary code, modify program behavior, or cause a crash.&#xA;Despite the introduction of modern security mechanisms such as ASLR and stack canaries, buffer overflow remains a critical topic in exploit development and pentesting.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>About</title>
      <link>https://pwnbuffer.org/en/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Feb 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://pwnbuffer.org/en/about/</guid>
      <description>🇧🇷 We are a Brazilian team of technology and hacking enthusiasts.&#xA;Discord: server&#xA;Youtube: youtube channel&#xA;X(Twitter): twitter&#xA;Github: github&#xA;&amp;ldquo;We believe that knowledge should be free&amp;rdquo; Link to heading </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Contribute your paper!</title>
      <link>https://pwnbuffer.org/en/contribute/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Feb 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://pwnbuffer.org/en/contribute/</guid>
      <description>▄████▄ ▒█████ ███▄ █ ▄▄▄█████▓ ██▀███ ██▓ ▄▄▄▄ █ ██ ▄▄▄█████▓▓█████ ▒██▀ ▀█ ▒██▒ ██▒ ██ ▀█ █ ▓ ██▒ ▓▒▓██ ▒ ██▒▓██▒▓█████▄ ██ ▓██▒▓ ██▒ ▓▒▓█ ▀ ▒▓█ ▄ ▒██░ ██▒▓██ ▀█ ██▒▒ ▓██░ ▒░▓██ ░▄█ ▒▒██▒▒██▒ ▄██▓██ ▒██░▒ ▓██░ ▒░▒███ ▒▓▓▄ ▄██▒▒██ ██░▓██▒ ▐▌██▒░ ▓██▓ ░ ▒██▀▀█▄ ░██░▒██░█▀ ▓▓█ ░██░░ ▓██▓ ░ ▒▓█ ▄ ▒ ▓███▀ ░░ ████▓▒░▒██░ ▓██░ ▒██▒ ░ ░██▓ ▒██▒░██░░▓█ ▀█▓▒▒█████▓ ▒██▒ ░ ░▒████▒ ░ ░▒ ▒ ░░ ▒░▒░▒░ ░ ▒░ ▒ ▒ ▒ ░░ ░ ▒▓ ░▒▓░░▓ ░▒▓███▀▒░▒▓▒ ▒ ▒ ▒ ░░ ░░ ▒░ ░ ░ ▒ ░ ▒ ▒░ ░ ░░ ░ ▒░ ░ ░▒ ░ ▒░ ▒ ░▒░▒ ░ ░░▒░ ░ ░ ░ ░ ░ ░ ░ ░ ░ ░ ▒ ░ ░ ░ ░ ░░ ░ ▒ ░ ░ ░ ░░░ ░ ░ ░ ░ ░ ░ ░ ░ ░ ░ ░ ░ ░ ░ ░ ░ ░ Do you have a paper on hacking or cybersecurity and want to share it with our audience?</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>black0ut</title>
      <link>https://pwnbuffer.org/en/m/black0ut/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://pwnbuffer.org/en/m/black0ut/</guid>
      <description> github: black0utzy&#xA;Note Hi my name is black0ut i&amp;rsquo;m specialist in web hacking, Kernel Hacking. Happy Hacking : ) </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>kz0x</title>
      <link>https://pwnbuffer.org/en/m/kz0x/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://pwnbuffer.org/en/m/kz0x/</guid>
      <description> ╱|、 (˚ˎ 。7 |、˜〵 じしˍ,)ノ github: Kz0x-337&#xA;Note Web hacking, exploit developer and Maldev </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Members</title>
      <link>https://pwnbuffer.org/en/members/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://pwnbuffer.org/en/members/</guid>
      <description> neurosys slayer kz0x zack tteuw愛 black0ut nullbyte raidboy </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>neurosys</title>
      <link>https://pwnbuffer.org/en/m/neurosys/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://pwnbuffer.org/en/m/neurosys/</guid>
      <description> github: n3ur0sys&#xA;Miserable&#xA;Note _._ _,-&amp;#39;&amp;#34;&amp;#34;`-._ (,-.`._,&amp;#39;( |\`-/| `-.-&amp;#39; \ )-`( , o o) `- \`_`&amp;#34;&amp;#39;- </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>nullbyte</title>
      <link>https://pwnbuffer.org/en/m/nullbyte/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://pwnbuffer.org/en/m/nullbyte/</guid>
      <description> github: NullByte-7w7&#xA;Note Codename NullByte, web, infra, low level. I really like maldev and love to understand how windows sysinternal works. </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>raidboy</title>
      <link>https://pwnbuffer.org/en/m/raidboy/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://pwnbuffer.org/en/m/raidboy/</guid>
      <description> github: 0xb0y426&#xA;Note Hello, my name is RAIDBOY and I have been in the programming and cyber security field for 4 years.I like low-level programming, operating systems, physics and Pokémon. </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>sl4yer</title>
      <link>https://pwnbuffer.org/en/m/slayer/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://pwnbuffer.org/en/m/slayer/</guid>
      <description> github: slayerkkkk&#xA;Note Hello, my name is Slayer. I have been in the cybersecurity area for 3 years and I am currently studying more about low level </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>tteuw愛</title>
      <link>https://pwnbuffer.org/en/m/tteuw/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://pwnbuffer.org/en/m/tteuw/</guid>
      <description> github: tteuw00111111&#xA;Note Software Dev, Maldev and Analysis, short reverse engineering as well. And a little bit of web (not enough) </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>wallpapers</title>
      <link>https://pwnbuffer.org/en/wallpapers/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://pwnbuffer.org/en/wallpapers/</guid>
      <description> ▄▄▄·▄▄▌ ▐ ▄▌ ▐ ▄ ▄▄▄▄· ▄• ▄▌·▄▄▄·▄▄▄▄▄▄ .▄▄▄ ▐█ ▄███· █▌▐█•█▌▐█▐█ ▀█▪█▪██▌▐▄▄·▐▄▄·▀▄.▀·▀▄ █· ██▀·██▪▐█▐▐▌▐█▐▐▌▐█▀▀█▄█▌▐█▌██▪ ██▪ ▐▀▀▪▄▐▀▀▄ ▐█▪·•▐█▌██▐█▌██▐█▌██▄▪▐█▐█▄█▌██▌.██▌.▐█▄▄▌▐█•█▌ .▀ ▀▀▀▀ ▀▪▀▀ █▪·▀▀▀▀ ▀▀▀ ▀▀▀ ▀▀▀ ▀▀▀ .▀ ▀ 1 2 3 4 5 6 7 8 9 10 </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>zack</title>
      <link>https://pwnbuffer.org/en/m/zack/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://pwnbuffer.org/en/m/zack/</guid>
      <description> github: Zack0x3&#xA;Note Web / Malware development and windows internals, addicted to lain.. </description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
