<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Low Level on pwnbuffer</title>
    <link>https://pwnbuffer.github.io/tags/low-level/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Low Level on pwnbuffer</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 05 Mar 2025 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="https://pwnbuffer.github.io/tags/low-level/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Rootkits in Firmware</title>
      <link>https://pwnbuffer.github.io/posts/slayer/rootkits-firmware/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 05 Mar 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://pwnbuffer.github.io/posts/slayer/rootkits-firmware/</guid>
      <description>What is a Rootkit? Link to heading A rootkit is a type of malware designed to gain and maintain privileged access to a system while hiding its presence. The term comes from the combination of &amp;ldquo;root&amp;rdquo;, which refers to the user with maximum privileges on Linux systems, and &amp;ldquo;kit&amp;rdquo; which represents a set of tools used to control the compromised system&#xA;The main purpose of a rootkit is to ensure persistence, allowing an attacker to continue accessing the system even after reboots or removal attempts.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>buffer overflow in practice</title>
      <link>https://pwnbuffer.github.io/posts/slayer/bof/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 07 Feb 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://pwnbuffer.github.io/posts/slayer/bof/</guid>
      <description>What is buffer overflow? Link to heading Buffer overflow (BOF) is one of the most wellknown and historically significant vulnerabilities in the world of cybersecurity. It occurs when a program writes more data to a buffer than it can hold, causing memory corruption. This flaw can be exploited by pentesters to execute arbitrary code, modify program behavior, or cause a crash.&#xA;Despite the introduction of modern security mechanisms such as ASLR and stack canaries, buffer overflow remains a critical topic in exploit development and pentesting.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
