<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Low Level on pwnbuffer</title>
    <link>https://pwnbuffer.org/en/tags/low-level/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Low Level on pwnbuffer</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 04 May 2025 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="https://pwnbuffer.org/en/tags/low-level/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>x86 Part. 2 — Number System</title>
      <link>https://pwnbuffer.org/en/posts/neurosys/x86-2/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 04 May 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://pwnbuffer.org/en/posts/neurosys/x86-2/</guid>
      <description>Welcome to the second part of our series of articles on Basic Reverse Engineering! Link to heading ██ ██ █████ ██████ ██ ██ ██ ██ ██ ███ █████ ███████ ██ ██ ██ ██ ██ ██ ██ ██ █████ ██████ Now that we&amp;rsquo;ve explored the fundamental concepts of CPU in the first article, it&amp;rsquo;s time to understand how data is represented and manipulated internally by computers. Let&amp;rsquo;s talk about numbering systems, with a focus on hexadecimal, which is crucial for those working with low-level reverse engineering.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Review of assembly</title>
      <link>https://pwnbuffer.org/en/posts/slayer/assembly-review/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 30 Apr 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://pwnbuffer.org/en/posts/slayer/assembly-review/</guid>
      <description>What is assembly? Link to heading Assembly is a low-level programming language, it is written to communicate directly with the processor hardware. Unlike high-level languages, such as the famous Python, assembly operates close to machine code, the famous binary! Each assembly instruction generally represents a single CPU operation, such as moving data between registers, performing arithmetic operations or controlling the flow of execution.&#xA;Assembly is not universal!! It depends directly on the processor architecture.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>x86 Part. 1 — CPU</title>
      <link>https://pwnbuffer.org/en/posts/neurosys/x86/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 30 Mar 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://pwnbuffer.org/en/posts/neurosys/x86/</guid>
      <description>This series of articles covers basic low-level concepts in computers, with a specific focus on exploring binaries and reverse engineering. Some points may seem confusing at first, but remember: everything follows a definition. Don’t get stuck in an endless loop of &amp;ldquo;why!?!&amp;rdquo; — just understand each concept and its purpose. You will use these concepts in reverse engineering, binary exploitation, and even malware development in the future.&#xA;What is a CPU?</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rootkits in Firmware</title>
      <link>https://pwnbuffer.org/en/posts/slayer/rootkits-firmware/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 05 Mar 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://pwnbuffer.org/en/posts/slayer/rootkits-firmware/</guid>
      <description>What is a Rootkit? Link to heading A rootkit is a type of malware designed to gain and maintain privileged access to a system while hiding its presence. The term comes from the combination of &amp;ldquo;root&amp;rdquo;, which refers to the user with maximum privileges on Linux systems, and &amp;ldquo;kit&amp;rdquo; which represents a set of tools used to control the compromised system&#xA;The main purpose of a rootkit is to ensure persistence, allowing an attacker to continue accessing the system even after reboots or removal attempts.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>buffer overflow in practice</title>
      <link>https://pwnbuffer.org/en/posts/slayer/bof/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 07 Feb 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://pwnbuffer.org/en/posts/slayer/bof/</guid>
      <description>What is buffer overflow? Link to heading Buffer overflow (BOF) is one of the most wellknown and historically significant vulnerabilities in the world of cybersecurity. It occurs when a program writes more data to a buffer than it can hold, causing memory corruption. This flaw can be exploited by pentesters to execute arbitrary code, modify program behavior, or cause a crash.&#xA;Despite the introduction of modern security mechanisms such as ASLR and stack canaries, buffer overflow remains a critical topic in exploit development and pentesting.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
